+91-9351881545 dukevaishnav3853@gmail.com

Duke Vaishnav

EXPERIENCE

Wipro — Database Administrator

FEB 2021 -- PRESENT

Core Technologies: Mysql, unix, Database Monitoring tools

Performing Data refresh / transfer , job related activities like execution, scheduling etc. ,deploying DDL/DML scripts on Database servers .

Troubleshooting errors on Database monitoring tools like - Oracle Enterprise Management(OEM)

Wipro — Java Developer

MARCH 2019 - JAN 2021

Core Technologies: Core java, Swing

Designing/Testing/Troubleshooting/upgrading code of a windows application for a reputed banking client

Contributed in representing the work done by team and giving ideas in client meetings

EDUCATION

Poornima college of engineering, Rajasthan — **B.tech in Computer Science** and **Engineering** MAY 2014 – FEB 2019

Percentage - 66.62 %

Learned multiple programming languages/paradigms, computer's hardware and software buildup, worked on projects, wonderful experience!!

All Saints Sr. Sec. School, Rajasthan — 12th

2013 - 2014

Percentage — 80.2%

All Saints Sr. Sec. School, Rajasthan — High School

2010 - 2012

CGPA - 9.2

PROJECTS (PORTFOLIO)

TeaTime (LINK) – News website which provide latest news of the day

Technology: Javascript, Html, Css, Bootstrap

Crypto Tracker (LINK) – Site displaying current price of all crypto currencies

Technology: ReactJS, Html, Css

Tic-Tac Toe game (LINK) —A simple game demonstrating ReactJS capabilities .

ABOUT

An aspiring full Stack Developer with 3 years of experience in database operations as a DBA along with good knowledge of frontend technologies like HTML, CSS, Javascript and fine experience attained during graduation in java, c, c++

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap Core Java, Swing C, C++ ReactJS

ACHIEVEMENTS

Won Delivery Excellence Award in Wipro, 2020

Participated in Infosys campus connect program during graduation

Secured 2nd position in circuit debugging event during graduation

HOBBIES

Playing Badminton
Outdoor walking/Running
Coding

LANGUAGES

Hindi, English

Technology: ReactJS, Html, Css

Calculator, Digital Clock (LINK) — Daily utility Apps

Technology: Core Java , Swing